<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kyle Gu</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kyle Gu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>library(tidyverse) library(&amp;quot;kableExtra&amp;quot;) nba_allstar &amp;lt;- read.csv(&amp;quot;https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;amp;id=1adb3W6h8KQRkLQ_X4Z39cG-zQtnuEiDy&amp;quot;) nba_attendance &amp;lt;- read.csv(&amp;quot;https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;amp;id=1ko3v_rGutSHIhPC_yXoSNOMkR7EaAEBg&amp;quot;) Introduction I selected two datasets from data.world: one for NBA All-Star player selections and another for NBA game attendance. The nba_allstar dataset contains the variables: year, player, player metrics (position, height, weight), team, conference, draft status, and nationalty. The nba_attendance dataset contains the variables: year, rank, team, and a variety of attendance variables for home and away games. All data were derived from the NBA&#39;s official records and basketball-reference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>0. Introduction ratings &amp;lt;- read.csv(&amp;quot;https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;amp;id=1k17J28AB-iPGyn3cFtbEU39r1MiPTPxJ&amp;quot;) The ratings dataset contains professor characteristics, course details, and evaluation scores for 463 courses taught during the 2000-2002 academic years at the University of Texas at Austin. There are 463 observations total, one for each course. The main variables that will be analyzed are: the age and gender of the professors, minority status (Caucasian or not), beauty (rating of professor&#39;s physical appearance averaged across 6 student panelists, mean-centered), native English speaker status (yes or no), division (upper or lower division course), tenure (whether or not the instructor is on tenure track), allstudents (number of students enrolled in the course), and course teaching evaluation score on a scale of 1 (very unsatisfactory) to 5 (excellent).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
